<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OVN, Open Virtual Network on OVN project documentation website</title>
    <link>/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in OVN, Open Virtual Network on OVN project documentation website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 09:46:30 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Long Term Support Releases</title>
      <link>/en/releases/long_term_support/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 09:46:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/releases/long_term_support/</guid>
      <description>The OVN project will periodically designate a release as &amp;ldquo;long-term support&amp;rdquo; or LTS for short. An LTS release has the distinction of being maintained for longer than a standard release.
LTS releases will receive bug fixes until the point that another LTS is released. At that point, the old LTS will receive an additional year of critical and security fixes. Critical fixes are those that are required to ensure basic operation (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 22.09.0</title>
      <link>/en/releases/release_22.09.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 08:53:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/releases/release_22.09.0/</guid>
      <description>In addition to bug fixes, the 22.09.0 release of OVN contains a mix of new features and performance improvements.
New Features Load balancers attached to logical routers have the option to automatically be applied to connected logical switches as well. When multiple requested chassis are used for a switch port, a RARP activation strategy has been implemented to allow for automatic switchover between the chassis. An IPsec option has been added to force NAT-T encapsulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 22.06.0</title>
      <link>/en/releases/release_22.06.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 08:53:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/releases/release_22.06.0/</guid>
      <description>In addition to bug fixes, the 22.06.0 release of OVN contains a mix of new features and performance improvements.
New Features Many features that made use of ct_label now use ct_mark. This allows for easier hardware offloading. NAT may now be configured on routers with multiple distributed gateway ports. MAC bindings may now be configured via the northbound database. &amp;ldquo;requested-chassis&amp;rdquo; now accepts a comma-separated list to allow for a port to be bound to multiple chassis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 22.03.0</title>
      <link>/en/releases/release_22.03.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Mar 2022 08:53:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/releases/release_22.03.0/</guid>
      <description>OVN 22.03.0 is a long term support (LTS) release. This version will receive bug fix support until the release of OVN 24.03.0, at which point it will receive one additional year of critical fixes.
In addition to bug fixes, the 22.03.0 release of OVN contains a mix of new features and performance improvements.
New Features ovn-ic now supports multicast flooding between AZs. The &amp;ndash;dummy-numa option for ovn-northd has been added. Control plan protection (CoPP) can now be named, allowing for easier referencing of policies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 21.12.0</title>
      <link>/en/releases/release_22.12.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 16:02:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/releases/release_22.12.0/</guid>
      <description>22.12.0 is mainly a stability release. The vast majority of commits were made with stabilization and fixing issues in mind.
In addition to bug fixes, the 21.12.0 release of OVN contains a mix of new features and performance improvements.
New Features There is a new option to automatically inherit load balancer groups from a logical router to its connected logical switches. A new load balancer affinity option has been added, which allows for a new load balancer backend to automatically be chosen after a configured time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 21.09.0</title>
      <link>/en/releases/release_21.09.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 08:53:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/releases/release_21.09.0/</guid>
      <description>In addition to bug fixes, the 21.09.0 release of OVN contains a mix of new features and performance improvements.
New Features OVN can now detect datapath features in OVS using the &amp;ldquo;Datapath&amp;rdquo; table in OVS. This is used to detect if all-zero SNAT is available. DHCP now supports option 12 (hostname). A limitation has been removed that now allows the full TCP/UDP port range (1-65535) rather than only half the range (1-32767) for Service Monitors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 21.06.0</title>
      <link>/en/releases/release_21.06.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 08:53:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/releases/release_21.06.0/</guid>
      <description>In addition to bug fixes, the 21.06.0 release of OVN contains a mix of new features and performance improvements.
New Features A new version of ovn-northd is included. This version is written in Differential Datalog instead of C and processes incrementally. VLAN passthru mode is supported. Custom 802.11ad support for localnet ports is added. An &amp;ldquo;allow-stateless&amp;rdquo; ACL option has been added that will always bypass conntrack. DNS now responds to PTR requests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 21.03.0</title>
      <link>/en/releases/release_21.03.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 08:53:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/releases/release_21.03.0/</guid>
      <description>In addition to bug fixes, the 21.03.0 release of OVN contains a mix of new features and performance improvements.
New Features When using the &amp;ldquo;reject&amp;rdquo; ACL verdict with SCTP, OVN now responds with an SCTP ABORT. OVN now supports &amp;ldquo;memory/show&amp;rdquo; via ovn-appct similar to OVS. OVN now supports using BFD on static routes to test liveness. See ovn-nb documentation for more details. Various ovn-nbctl enhancements lr-route-list gives a BFD report lr-route-list gives ECMP and ECMP symmetric reply information lr-lb-add option now has an &amp;ndash;event option to enable controller events for empty backends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 20.12.0</title>
      <link>/en/releases/release_20.12.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2020 08:53:48 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/releases/release_20.12.0/</guid>
      <description>In addition to numerous bug fixes, the 20.12.0 release of OVN contains a mix of new features and performance improvements.
New Features Add support for DHCP RENEW/REBIND for IPv6 prefix delegation (RFC 3633). DHCP iPXE support has been added. A new vlan-passthru option has been added to logical switches to allow vlan-tagged incoming traffic. DHCP option 28 (broadcast address) support has been added. The conntrack zone used by a gateway router for SNAT can now be explicitly configured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 20.09.0</title>
      <link>/en/releases/release_20.09.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 08:53:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/releases/release_20.09.0/</guid>
      <description>In addition to numerous bug fixes, the 20.09.0 release of OVN contains a mix of new features and performance improvements.
New Features Allow the lb_force_snat_ip and dnat_force_snat_ip options to take an IPv4 and IPv6 address pair. This may be needed for dual stack setups. DHCP now understands DHCPDECLINE External IP based NAT. This allows for a set of IPs to be used for SNAT instead of always SNATting to a single external IP address.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
